<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Conscious</string>
    <string name="app_logo_please">I need an app logo please as well as some color : )</string>
    <string name="userName">username</string>
    <string name="password">password</string>
    <string name="register">Not already a user? Sign up to register</string>
    <string name="login">login</string>
    <string name="sign_up">sign Up</string>
    <string name="remember_check_bx">Remember Login</string>
    <string name="body_smart">Body Smart</string>
    <string name="music_smart">Music Smart</string>
    <string name="nature_smart">Nature Smart</string>
    <string name="number_smart">Number Smart</string>
    <string name="people_smart">People Smart</string>
    <string name="picture_smart">Picture Smart</string>
    <string name="self_smart">Self Smart</string>
    <string name="word_smart">Word Smart</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="email">email</string>
    <string name="here_is_the_favorites_activity_that_extends_fragment">Here is the favorites activity that extends fragment.</string>
    <string name="disclaimer">What you are about to engage in is the opportunity to
                              progress your current daily behavioral patterns. You have
                                found yourself here because at some point you knew you could
                            do better and be better as a human being in life. </string>
    <string name="disclaimer2">In no way does this app diagnose, cure or counsel it\'s users.
                            In every way, does this app advocate and cheer you on in the direction you know you need to go.</string>
    
    
    <string name="body_smart_card_1"> Try studying while moving or exercising</string>
    <string name="body_smart_card2"> Try using physical motions to articulate vocabulary and key concepts</string>
    <string name="body_smart_card3"> Try to draw or write things in the air as you think about them</string>
    <string name="body_smart_card4"> Write concepts/terms down in your own words</string>
    <string name="body_smart_card5"> Act out the any concepts you need to remember</string>
    <string name="body_smart_card6"> Utilize manipulative and interactive web material to master difficult concepts</string>
    <string name="body_smart_card7"> Look for real-life examples that demonstrate what you’re learning about</string>

    <string name="music_smart_card1"> Create a song, rap, or rhyme that will help you remember difficult concepts</string>
    <string name="music_smart_card2"> Listen to instrumental music while you study</string>
    <string name="music_smart_card3"> Remember vocabulary words by linking them to similar-sounding words in your mind</string>
    <string name="music_smart_card4"> Read text and notes aloud and repeat when it doesn’t makes sense</string>
    <string name="music_smart_card5"> Try saying concepts or definitions aloud with your eyes closed</string>
    <string name="music_smart_card6"> create a Music Video</string>
    
    <string name="nature_smart_card1"> Try to be in or near nature when studying</string>
    <string name="nature_smart_card2"> Try to connect vocabulary to nature</string>

    <string name="number_smart_card1"> Organize chapter notes into an outline (roman numeral style)</string>
    <string name="number_smart_card2"> Transform your notes into numeric charts, graphs, and tables.</string>
    <string name="number_smart_card3"> Put information you receive into categories and classifications that you create</string>
    <string name="number_smart_card4"> Compare/contrast previously learned items with new concepts (rock cycle vs. carbon and nitrogen cycles)</string>
    <string name="number_smart_card5"> Formulate analogies to describe abstract or complex ideas</string>
    <string name="number_smart_card6"> Devise a mnemonic device to help remember methods or multi-faceted definitions/terms</string>

    <string name="people_smart_card1"> Discuss what you learn with a friend or family member</string>
    <string name="people_smart_card2"> Have someone quiz you before an exam</string>
    <string name="people_smart_card3"> Create or join a study group</string>
    <string name="people_smart_Card4"> Go over section assessment chapter test questions from book with others</string>
    <string name="people_smart_card5"> Avoid being alone when you try to study (only if your intrapersonal intelligence is weak)</string>
    <string name="people_smart_card6"> Read about or watch videos on others’ ideas on difficult topics (Google, YouTube, etc.)</string>
    <string name="people_smart_card7"> Share ideas with friends</string>
    <string name="people_smart_card8"> Partake in the Extra Credit Music Video Assignment with some friends</string>

    <string name="picture_smart_card1"> Sketch pictures that go along with your notes or in the margins of your textbooks</string>
    <string name="picture_smart_card2"> Draw a picture on a flashcard for each concept or vocabulary word you study</string>
    <string name="picture_smart_card3"> Design charts, tables, diagrams, foldables, and/or other graphic organizers to organize and keep track of what you learn</string>
    <string name="picture_smart_card4"> Picture images and scenarios in your mind to associate with different concepts and ideas</string>
    <string name="picture_smart_card5"> Re-watch videos from class</string>
    <string name="picture_smart_card6"> Make visual flash cards to study vocabulary and key concepts</string>

    <string name="self_smart_card1"> Find a place to study alone where you won’t be interrupted (avoid group studying)</string>
    <string name="self_smart_card2"> Study in quiet places(unless your musical intelligence in high in which case light instrumentals may help)</string>
    <string name="self_smart_card3"> Talk to yourself or an inanimate object about key concepts</string>
    <string name="self_smart_card4"> Reflect upon and correct handouts, book questions, and study guide by yourself</string>
    <string name="self_smart_card5"> Use google to complete self-check quizzes for each section</string>
    <string name="self_smart_card6"> Keep a daily personal journal on what you learn</string>
    
    <string name="word_smart_card1"> Make flashcards for vocabulary AND key concepts (speak aloud when self-quizzing)</string>
    <string name="word_smart_card2"> Read textbook, notes (ones you took in class and from PowerPoint on website), handouts, etc. (repeat if necessary)</string>
    <string name="word_smart_card3"> Take extra notes on tougher parts of chapter(s)</string>
    <string name="word_smart_card4"> Rewrite key concepts and definitions</string>
    <string name="word_smart_card5"> Orally summarize section to another person (friend, parent, etc.)</string>
    <string name="word_smart_card6"> Re-organize class notes</string>
    <string name="word_smart_card7"> Orally recite definitions and key concepts</string>



</resources>
